[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "What's the motivation for you when you have those kind of open, free clinics?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "Piers, I get letters in the mail daily from folks who say you are my doctor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "How does America look after its most needy people with a system that often doesn't allow them to have anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "Everyone has to be in the system.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "Eighty million people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "Eighty million people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "What's the simple answer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "The simple answer is the most expensive thing we do in medicine is provide bad care.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "How restrictive is that to you as a practitioner?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "It's usually restrictive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "Comparative to, say, other main countries, major countries in the world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "TO", ",", "VB", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "You know, again, using your scaling system, I would probably give us an 80.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "Let me ask you a question -- well, you didn't grow up in this country, but I think our viewers might resonate to this, and so I ask this to you directly -- did you walk to school when you were a kid?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "TO", "PRP", "RB", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Dr. Oz?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Or pre-op.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "So, how good is that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "One-thirty-four/eighty-two is average for America.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "CD", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "What should I be looking for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "One-fifteen over 75 is the optimal number.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "What the hell are you talking about, Dr. Oz?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "What an error.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "One example, skim milk, good for you or bad for you if you're going to lose weight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "I'm sure you're about to tell you it's not good for you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "What is the best milk to drink?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "Drink regular milk, just drink less of it, because it's real food.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "How many preservatives are in this food?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Many of the preservatives good for shelf life but they're bad for human life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["70 percent"]}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "JJ", "CD", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "CC", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "What are the biggest problems Americans facing with health they could easily fix, what are the most common mistakes people make with their health?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "NNPS", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "Five major themes that drive 70 percent of how long and how well we age.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "DT", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "What is the best way to lose weight without having to just eat carrots?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "Well, first off, carbohydrates, I do think we have a problem with simple carbohydrates, the simple sugars, the white foods, white rice, white pasta, the whites that we bake with, these are all problems for us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", ":", "VBN", ",", "EX", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "Because it's too dramatic, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "Your body is geared -- listen, there a dozen systems to keep you eating.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "Focus primarily on losing 100 calories a day from the way would you normally lead your life, what kind of results would you see and what kind of time span?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "Just give you an idea of 100 calories, half a doughnut, half a soft drink, a small little nudgy move like that will take off about 12 or 13 pounds a year.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "How old are you, if you don't mine me asking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Fifty-one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", ",", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "Which is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "Which is around 6:00, about 5:00 or 6:00 for reason I come to in a second.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "Seven?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "Seven.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["morning"]}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "RP", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Seven minutes is enough?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "Seven minutes is enough to get you going in the morning, to get your metabolism up, to get my pushups and sit-up with us my stretching exercises, I feel like I control what I'm doing the rest of the day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "So, do you go to the gym at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "Do you run?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "How are you going to deal with my cravings?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "Well, first, alcohol has a longevity benefit, without question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Is it true that red wine is better for you than white wine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RBR", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "It's absolutely true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "What are the good things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "I always have nuts in my pocket.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "Any nut good?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "I like Walnuts, but I like the taste.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "There's no way you can block that off.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RBS", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "What if you absolutely love bread?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "Well, most people will have a problem with too much bread.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "I'm good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "How much of it, if you are honest, was shock marketing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", ",", "VBD", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "Uh, almost all of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "TO", ":", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "When it goes that big and you've had a bit of fun with the title and it's obviously deliberately shocking, does any part of you slightly feel, well, maybe we should have been a bit more careful here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "Well, I guess the -- the consideration we took was to -- to prerecord the alternative versions for radio and elsewhere, just in the event that the song, you know, did connect in some way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "That is with people, you know what I'm saying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "It certainly did that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "When you're 18 years old and you effectively -- you have now been orphaned, what does that do to a young man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "It's definitely a rude -- a very rude awakening.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "What do you think she would have made of your extraordinary success?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "I think she would have been the best manager ever.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "She would be pretty proud of you, wouldn't she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "I think she still is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "WP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "Do you feel that she is a constant presence?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Yes, I think she is definitely alive in all of this positive energy surrounding what's become of me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "What was going on in this mad world that you were then occupying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "Well, I will correct one of those statements.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "-- sort of slightly out of control?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "Is that overstating it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "No, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "How did you transform into this Cee Lo?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "Well, I definitely -- again, my mother's passing, you know, had a lot to do with me committing myself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "Would you stop being modest, please?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "JJS", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "That's it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "You have got two diamonds, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "NNS", "VBG", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "Dare I ask how much they are worth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "It's about -- a gentleman never tells, but we are friends and we are not -- people talking, right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "Can you trust women?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "MD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "If you -- if you are honest with yourself, it is very hard for people to lie to you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "CC", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "What are values that make a good America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "I guess, you know, it would be, you know, a matter of just share and share alike and earning your keep and all of those good old-fashioned quotables that you could apply to the conversation of just, you know, what's fair is fair and blah, blah, blah.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 620, "question": "Are you a big Tweeter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 621, "answer": "I'm not a big Tweeter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 624, "question": "How many followers have you got?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 625, "answer": "I have about a million followers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "It makes sense.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120518pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "RB", ",", "RBS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 664, "question": "Can you promise that I get an invite if you're going to have the mother of all parties?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 665, "answer": "Most certainly, most certainly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]